<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Dan Writes]]></title>
  <link href="http://InTheBlue.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://InTheBlue.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2013-05-09T20:40:27+00:00</updated>
  <id>http://InTheBlue.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Daniel Wright]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[A feeling like no other]]></title>
    <link href="http://InTheBlue.github.io/blog/2013/05/09/a-feeling-like-no-other/"/>
    <updated>2013-05-09T19:53:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://InTheBlue.github.io/blog/2013/05/09/a-feeling-like-no-other</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Today marks my first time on a motorbike, a Suzuki SV650 to be specific. I wasn&#8217;t the driver, I was riding pillion while my housemate Rich was in control. Before I even got on the bike I had to work hard to remain calm and not think about how snug and claustrophobic the helmet felt. In a way it was fairly reassuring to know how secure my heat was, but I&#8217;ve never been good in confined spaces. Rich breifed me on the do&#8217;s and don&#8217;ts before we set off, making sure I knew to keep stil and not fidget if the bike was moving slowly or was stationary.</p>

<p>I was immediately surprised by how wind there was around us, not just from us moving forwards, but a strong crosswind as well and that unnerved me for a while. Then that took a backseat while I was being stunned by how quickly the bike could accelerate. After a while I stopped thinking about the helmet, ignored the bumps in the road, didn&#8217;t care about the huge amount of wind around me and embraced the feeling of flying along on what felt like a guided missile.</p>

<p>I&#8217;ve never felt anything like it and I&#8217;ve not had that much fun in a very long time. And then it was over before I knew it, Rich had somewhere he needed to be, so we&#8217;d only done town roads. But in a few weeks we should be riding up to Huntingdon for a blast down some winding roads. And I can&#8217;t wait.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction]]></title>
    <link href="http://InTheBlue.github.io/blog/2013/05/08/introduction/"/>
    <updated>2013-05-08T19:08:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://InTheBlue.github.io/blog/2013/05/08/introduction</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>My name is Daniel Wright and I&#8217;m a Computer Science undergraduate at Nottingham Trent University, currently on Industrial Placement at ARM as a Software Engineer.</p>

<p>I&#8217;ll be using this blog to post things I hope that someone else will find useful or interesting including: Software Development, Python, Git, Photography and Food.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
